    var  questions =[
        {
            id : "1", 
            category :"development",
            question :"What is the project about, type of project and high level scope?" ,
            answer : "Understand uber level scope of the project, the type of project and the accountability etc." , 
            priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {
            id : "2", 
            category :"development",
            question :"What are your external and internal dependencies?" ,
            answer : "Internal and external dependencies needs to be called out properly - be it design, services, data, environment." , 
            priority : "Optional" , 
        },
        {
            id : "3", 
            category :"accessibility",
                    question :"When a blind person using a white cane, enters your store, how should you approach that person, and/or offer assistance? ",
            answer : "If the person appears to be be having 
difficulty, ask first “Can I help you?” If the 
person answers yes, ask “How can I help you best?” and follow their lead. Never assume a blind person, or any other person with a disability, needs help. Some people will not want to be helped, preferring independence. 
" , 
            priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "4", 
        category :"accessibility",
        question :"What standard are the web accessibility requirements of The Information and Communication Standard, and other regulations around the world, typically governed by? " ,
        answer : "The W3C Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG 2) " , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "5", 
        category :"development",
        question :"Which CMSs have you worked with?" ,
        answer : "Some common open-source content management systems (CMSs) are WordPress, Joomla and Drupal. To elicit more information, ask if they’re involved in the relevant open-source communities and whether they’ve ever made any contributions. " , 
        priority : "Optional" , 
        },
        {id : "6", 
        category :"development",
        question :"What are the localization requirements?" ,
        answer : "Will solution need to work with multiple languages? If yes, then corresponding design needs to be validated with some kind of actual data so that any gaps in the design can be identified prior signing up for the solution.
Non of the data ownership lies with client and we should data sources available." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "7", 
        category :"accessibility",
        question :"How would you make an image in a webpage accessible to someone who is blind? " ,
        answer : "Add alt text to the image HTML to describe the meaningful elements of the image, and if necessary provide a more detailed description in a caption or in the surrounding text." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "8", 
        category :"development",
        question :"What are NFRs for Analytics?" ,
        answer : "Event level data capture or will it be page level?" , 
        priority : "Optional" , 
        },
        {id : "9", 
        category :"functional",
        question :"Between JavaScript and an ASP script, which is faster?" ,
        answer : "JavaScript is faster. JavaScript is a client-side language and thus it does not need the assistance of the web server to execute. On the other hand, ASP is a server-side language and hence is always slower than JavaScript. Javascript now is also a server side language (nodejs)." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "10", 
        category :"functional",
        question :"What are undeclared and undefined variables?" ,
        answer : "Undeclared variables are those that do not exist in a program and are not declared. If the program tries to read the value of an undeclared variable, then a runtime error is encountered.
Undefined variables are those that are declared in the program but have not been given any value. If the program tries to read the value of an undefined variable, an undefined value is returned" , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
            {id : "11", 
        category :"functional",
        question :"What is a prompt box?" ,
        answer : "A prompt box is a box which allows the user to enter input by providing a text box. Label and box will be provided to enter the text or number." , 
        priority : "Optional" , 
        },
        {id : "12", 
        category :"functional",
        question :"Explain the difference between "==" and "==="?" ,
        answer : ""==" checks only for equality in value whereas "===" is a stricter equality test and returns false if either the value or the type of the two variables are different." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "13", 
        category :"accessibility",
        question :"What can be done to ensure that people with disabilities have an equal opportunity to apply for jobs as their able peers?  " ,
        answer : "Employers should inform applicants that accommodations are available on request in relation to materials and processes used. " , 
        priority : "Optional" , 
        },
        {id : "14", 
        category :"functional",
        question :"What are JavaScript Cookies?" ,
        answer : "Cookies are the small test files stored in a computer and it gets created when the user visits the websites to store information that they need. Example could be User Name details and shopping cart information from the previous visits." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },
        {id : "15", 
        category :"accessibility",
        question :"What accessibility knowledge is needed by staff who are producing documents for public distribution? " ,
        answer : "Be able to use the accessibility test tools in Word, or in Acrobat Pro for example, to test and make adjustments to documents." , 
        priority : "Mandatory" , 
        },

    ]